videodefine.com 2019-07-09

# Video Define - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

www.videodefine.com (the "Site") is brought to you by Video Define Media, Inc. ("we" or "us"). This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal and non-personal information we collect on the Site, how we use such information and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it. By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the policy, please do not use the Site.

###### Collection of Information

We collect personal information from you when you submit it to us, including by: (1) registering on the Site; (2) submitting a video or other content to the Site; (3) contacting us; (4) participating in a Site promotion; or (5) registering for our filmmaker program. This information may include, for example, your name, address, email address, other contact information, date of birth, credentials, other biographical information and photograph. 

If you use the Site's refer-a-friend mechanism, we will collect your friend's email address, solely for the purposes of sending the email and monitoring use of the refer-a-friend mechanism. 

We may combine the information we collect from you online with information we collect about you offline, such as from address update services. 

When you visit the Site, we may collect certain non-personally-identifiable information from you, including your IP address, browser type and language, the domain name from which you accessed the Site and the date and time of your visit. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other clickstream data. 

We may use cookies to collect the non-personal information described above. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the Site. We may also use cookies to: (1) allow you to use the Site without having to re-enter your user name and password; (2) monitor Site usage; (3) manage the Site; and (4) improve the Site and our services. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site. Check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

We may also use web beacons on the Site, in our emails and in our advertisements on other websites. Web beacons are tiny graphic images that are used to collect information about your Site visit, such as the pages you view and the features you use, as well as information about whether you open and/or act upon one of our emails or advertisements. Web beacons help us analyze our Site visitors' behavior and measure the effectiveness of the Site and our advertising. We may work with service providers that help us track, collect and analyze this information. In addition, we may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site and to serve our advertisements across the Internet. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to the Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

###### Use & Disclosure of Information

Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily upload or submit for posting to the Site (including your user name and information in your videos, bios, blogs, messaging and in comments you post to others' videos) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. It is in violation of the Site's Terms of Use for you to post any content that requests personally identifiable information. We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to post your video to the Site and identify you as the creator; (2) to respond to your inquiries; (3) to contact you when necessary; (4) to review Site usage and operations; (5) to address problems with the Site, our business or our services; and (6) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business. We may also use your information to contact you with Site updates, newsletters and other informational and promotional materials from us, as well as from other companies. You may choose not to receive promotional email from us by following the unsubscribe instructions in each message. We may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our related companies and service providers, to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (3) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (4) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. We may also disclose your personal information with your express consent. 

We may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about Site users with third parties. 

###### Security

There is no such thing as perfect security on the Internet. However, we have taken certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Site visitors. 

###### Children

We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen. 

###### Third Party Websites

The Site may contain links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any site that you may access through the Site. 

###### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on our website. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate online notice to you. 

###### CONTACT US

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us
